<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <title>Your Title - </title>
 <link href="http://example.com/blog/tags/faq/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://example.com/tag/.html"/>
 <updated>2014-08-05T15:56:40-06:00</updated>
 <id>http://example.com/tag/.html</id>
 <author>
   <name>Author Here</name>
 </author>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I&#8217;m getting a new phone. How can I transfer my data</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2013/11/25/im-getting-a-new-phone-how-can-i-transfer-my-data/"/>
   <updated>2013-11-25T08:59:48-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2013/11/25/im-getting-a-new-phone-how-can-i-transfer-my-data</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Option 1:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div&gt;If you have the same gmail account in both phones: Go to backup, tap on backup on the old phone, wait a few seconds and then on the new phone: go to back up and then hit the Restore button.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Option 2:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div&gt;You have multiple backups in your sd card: Copy the folder named: 90Droid from the old phone to the new one. Then go to the Back up screen and tap Restore from SD.&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>90Droid on Kindle Fire</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2012/01/02/90droid-on-kindle-fire/"/>
   <updated>2012-01-02T08:30:24-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2012/01/02/90droid-on-kindle-fire</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We have found the problem that makes the Kindle Fire force close with 90Droid. To prevent it please do the following: Main Screen &gt; Preferences &gt; (Uncheck) Disable auto key lock. Please let us know if you have any other questions/comments. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
Team 90Droid &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How do I track X2 with 90Droid?</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2012/01/02/how-do-i-track-x2-with-90droid/"/>
   <updated>2012-01-02T08:08:42-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2012/01/02/how-do-i-track-x2-with-90droid</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;From the main screen go to Programs &gt; Menu &gt; Download More.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There you&#39;ll find many exercise programs shared by the community, such as P90X2, Hybrids, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that, P90X2 is a trademark of Beachbody, you&#39;ll need the DVDs for instruction on how to do the exercises. And we are not related to Beachbody in any way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy&lt;br /&gt;
Team 90Droid&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>90Droid Community</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2011/12/07/90droid-community/"/>
   <updated>2011-12-07T21:16:16-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2011/12/07/90droid-community</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congrats everybody that got an early copy of P90X2. We are relying on our community to collaborate and share the workouts so we can all build the schedule together. You can see the shared programs in Programs &gt; Download Program. If you are interested in sharing part of the schedule, please use use Programs &gt; Menu &gt; New Program then Long Tap on the Program Name and Share. We are sure we&#39;ll complete it very soon. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
Team 90Droid&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What is the Account/Internet Permission used for?</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2011/07/21/what-is-the-accountinternet-permission-used-for/"/>
   <updated>2011-07-21T19:25:03-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2011/07/21/what-is-the-accountinternet-permission-used-for</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The app requires permissions to your google account so you don&#39;t have to manually sign in whenever you want to do a back up to/restore from the cloud. Please note that all we do is ask google for a token to see if your account is valid so we can store your data securely and nobody else has access to it. We however, don&#39;t get access to your password or personal information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The internet permission is also used to back up/restore from the cloud, as well as for validating the license and gathering anonymous information on the performance of the app. Rest assured that we don&#39;t share any data with third parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Team 90Droid.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How do I start over?</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2011/05/24/how-do-i-start-over/"/>
   <updated>2011-05-24T13:48:19-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2011/05/24/how-do-i-start-over</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve been getting this question since version 1. That&#39;s why we created the Cycles module, here is how it works:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A cycle is nothing but a range of dates for a specific program. for example: P90X Classic from January 1st to March 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It doesn&#39;t have to cover the whole program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can set the start and end dates that you want.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you set a cycle as active, your records will be filtered to display only the ones within that date range.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having said that, if you want to &quot;start over&quot;, all you need to do is create a new cycle, set the starting date as today and make it active, that will only show what you do from now on. So,  if you want to go back and see what you did before, you can change the dates in the cycle or you can mark it as inactive in the edit screen.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I do more than 40 reps, how do I track them?</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2011/05/11/i-do-more-than-40-reps-how-do-i-track-them/"/>
   <updated>2011-05-11T21:29:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2011/05/11/i-do-more-than-40-reps-how-do-i-track-them</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Go to the main screen&lt;br /&gt;
Hit the menu key&lt;br /&gt;
Select preferences&lt;br /&gt;
Tap on max reps and type your new maximum&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How do I change the program (Classic, Doubles, Lean)</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2011/05/11/how-do-i-change-the-program-classic-doubles-lean/"/>
   <updated>2011-05-11T14:20:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2011/05/11/how-do-i-change-the-program-classic-doubles-lean</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In order to change the program please do the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to the main screen (The one with the list of days)&lt;br /&gt;
Then press the menu key on your phone&lt;br /&gt;
From the menu you can select Preferences&lt;br /&gt;
There you can select the program from the list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting v 4.0 we added &#39;program manager&#39; to the main menu, it  will show you the list of programs. Long-tap on the one you want and set as active. Hit back, you&#39;ll see the change in the days&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>90Droid is not saving my workouts</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2011/04/18/90droid-is-not-saving-my-workouts-after-the-update/"/>
   <updated>2011-04-18T21:19:36-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2011/04/18/90droid-is-not-saving-my-workouts-after-the-update</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Symptom: When you hit save on a workout then hit prev to see the results, you don&#39;t see the item in the history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your workout is being saved it&#39;s just not showing in the &quot;previous&quot; list&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solution: go to Cycles and make sure that the active cycle includes today&#39;s date. The easiest way to do this is to leave the end-date empty, that will include everything from the start date on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We created cycles to help you filter previous workouts without having to delete them. If you set a cycle as active but the end-date does not include today&#39;s date, the history list will not display them. All you will see is a warning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Addendum: We have created a new post that can give you some other clues: &lt;a title=&quot;Filtering Records&quot; href=&quot;http://www.unifylog.com/?p=445&quot;&gt;Filtering Records&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Team 90Droid.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>90Droid says it&#8217;s not installed after update</title>
   <link href="http://example.com/blog/2011/04/15/90droid-says-its-not-installed-after-update/"/>
   <updated>2011-04-15T11:22:06-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://example.com/blog/2011/04/15/90droid-says-its-not-installed-after-update</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some 90Droid users have reported that the only way to access the app is to go to the Android Market and launch it from there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this happens to you please do the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the app (by going to the market),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Backup your workouts (&lt;strong&gt;Make sure you get a success message&lt;/strong&gt;) If backup doesn&#39;t work for any reason stop here and send us an email&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uninstall the app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to the market and download it again&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to Restore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you follow this instructions you will get the app to work and you won&#39;t lose any data. The cause for this problem is a change in the licensing service for Android. Unfortunately we don&#39;t have control over this within the App. We are sorry for this inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let us know if you have any questions or problems with this approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Team 90Droid&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
</feed>